Guilbert Plaza

San Juan City, NCR 1500 • +63 969 063 2381 • plaza.guilbert@outlook.com

Customer Service Representative

Transforming the business process industry with over 7 years of full-time experience and a trailblazing record of accomplishments is a testament to unparalleled passion for pushing the boundaries of customer satisfaction and streamlining processes to a level of absurdity that has never been seen.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

SITEL GROUP, Mandaluyong, MM

TECHNICAL SUPPORT SPECIALIST (October 2020 – December 2022)

Facilitated technical support for thousands of Hewlett-Packard Enterprise systems located in North America over the past two years, as pertaining to FTC's Bureau of Consumer Protection.

ACCENTURE, Quezon City, MM

COLLECTION ADVISOR SPECIALIST (October 2017 – July 2020)

Conducted Virgin Media's collection statistics and implements optimized strategies to prevent flow through of accounts, control delinquencies, maximize bad debt recovery, minimize specific provisions, and exert comprehensive control over the customer debt collection process.

IBEX, Mandaluyong, MM

CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE (June 2017 – September 2017)

Involved in Verizon's technical aspects of debt collection and dispute resolution. Managed both inbound and outbound customer interactions, utilizing advanced communication skills and technical aptitude with a focus on mitigating disputes on client's account statement.

CONVERGYS, Mandaluyong, MM

TECHNICAL SUPPORT REPRESENTATIVE (October 2016 – April 2017)

Assessed American Telephone and Telegraph Company clients' with technical troubleshooting and account management, leveraging suite of software tools and data repositories to access and preserve customer information, ensuring the maintenance of records.

TRANSCOM, Mandaluyong, MM

CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE (March 2015 – October 2016)

Responsible for managing various TalkTalk (a telecommunications company based on United Kingdom) clients' issues including transactions related to client inquiries, product support or inbound sales, as well as updating Information Technology Infrastructure for customer demographics.

EDUCATION & CREDENTIALS

THE UNIVERSITY OF MANILA, Manila, Philippines

Bachelor of Science; Major: Accountancy, March 2000

Industry Knowledge Skills

Client Issue Resolution • Debt Collection • CRM/ERP • Internet Protocol Addressing • Private Branch Exchange • Remote Troubleshooting • Telecommunications • Microsoft Dynamics 365